Wash It
All Away
Episode 3       Closed All Day Today
Thank you very much.
Let's try not to fail any subjects
with the festival coming up, yeah?
Yeah. See you.
You bet. Later, man.
It looks dark inside too.
I wonder what could have happened.
Hello there.
How's it goin'?
Oh, Kyu-chan. You're back early today.
Well, it's finals week.
Is there some reason
why you're all standing around here?
Actually, you've got perfect timing.
You see, it's a regular business day,
but Kinme-san hasn't opened her shop yet.
We are closed for the day.
So we were all wondering about
what could have happened to her.
Mhm.
Right...
Yes. So we'd like your help, Kyu-chan.
Well? Can you see inside the room?
No, not yet.
Is this... okay?
Oh, it's open.
Um, excuse me.
Kinme-san?
Um...
Uh... are you all right?
My!
Oh dear.
Well, she sounds all right.
Everything's fine.
She was only sleeping.
Nothin' to worry about.
I'm glad it turned out to be nothing.
I suppose she just overslept after all.
Oh no! You're kidding!
U-Uh, I'm very sorry for
coming in without permission.
Don't tell me that stuff
from last night did me in.
Huh? Stuff?
Yesterday, I picked up
a number of items from a customer,
and among them was one
very unique and delicate piece
that required extra time and care to wash.
I was so proud of myself
after accomplishing such a big job,
I must have let it go to my head.
Then, one of my regulars showed up before
closing time and invited me out to dinner.
And I just... jumped at the chance.
Welcome
Restaurant with an Ocean View
And then...
I was so excited to try out
a new restaurant,
I even ordered a drink,
which I almost never do.
With the first drink—
no, with the first sip,
my mind went completely blank.
I had no idea I was actually
such a lightweight.
Turmeric
Extract
Turmeric pills?
When and how did I even make it back?
Did I make my customer carry me home?
Huh.
So I guess you really like
to let loose sometimes.
N-No, I do not!
I absolutely do not l-let loose at all!
Oh!
Uh, what time is it right now?
I-It is still morning, right?
Huh? Oh... It's around noon.
Is she all right, though?
I'm going downstairs
to tend to the customers.
K-Kyusho-kun,
just make yourself at home up here.
Yeah. Make myself at home?
So please excuse me.
Oh.
Thank you very much for waking me up.
Yeah. No big deal.
She's not mad that I snuck in like that?
And I need to ask you for one favor.
Will you promise not to tell anyone that
I fell asleep in such a slovenly manner?
Uh... oh, sure.
It's not really something
I'd go around telling people anyway.
P-Promise me.
Um, wow.
I haven't made a pinkie promise since...
what, kindergarten maybe?
Welcome!
2x Points
Every Tuesday
Welcome!
2x Points
Every Tuesday
I washed it, but it still isn't clean!
Well...
that's because of a mismatch
between the kind of stain
and your type of cleaning!
At Kinme Cleaning, we use
washing methods tailored
to the exact type of
cleaning you need.
I sincerely apologize.
It's fine, dear.
We know you have a lot
on your hands, Kinme-san.
Hello, this is Kinme Cleaning.
Oh, no, not at all.
I apologize that I was unable
to answer the phone this morning.
Yes, a pick-up?
C'mere, c'mere.
Yes.
Good job, Kyu-chan!
Of course.
Here's a little reward for you.
I see.
Oh, thank you.
In that case, we should move quickly.
Yes. Yes.
Haven't had these
since kindergarten, either.
Yes. I could be there...
Yes. Yes. Five o'clock is fine.
Yes, perfectly all right. Yes.
I probably shouldn't distract her now.
Of course! Understood.
You can count on Kinme.
So, have you tried
that new restaurant yet?
Holy...
I figured I should check in on her,
but what's with the crowd?
So quickly, I know!
Young man there.
Uh, yes?
You just came out of the cleaners, right?
Would you happen to know
something about this?
No, not exactly.
It seems like Kinme-san
overslept for once.
Oh, you don't say.
I did give her some turmeric pills
when we went home.
I hope she remembered to take some.
For Liver Health!
Turmeric Extract Tablets
Turmeric?
Huh? Yeah.
I invited Kinme-san out
to dinner last night.
Is this the regular she was talking about?
And get this, Kinme-san said
she'd never had alcohol before,
but she didn't get drunk at all
and was walking perfectly fine
on the way home.
So I'm betting she didn't oversleep
because I got her drunk or anything.
I really apologize for this.
Don't worry about it.
By the way, young man,
are you one of her customers?
You look more like a student to me.
I just happened to be passing by.
I noticed the shop was still closed,
so I went in through the second floor
and woke her up. That's all.
The second floor, huh.
I have to rush back to work right now,
but tell Kinme-san I said hi, okay?
Uh, sure.
Ow!
You'd better be careful
not to fall for her or anything, got it?
Bye!
What does someone like that
do for a living?
Guesthouse Inn Ishimochi
Here ya go.
I thought the customers had more kids
than they did and made one too many.
Now clean your plate, okay?
Another first since kindergarten.
Wash It All Away
Closed all day today.
Good morning, Poly-chan!
Okay.
Marion
Cleaner
Good.
Phew.
For the shop, I like to make
new posters and flyers every season.
I get more active with sales campaigns
when there's a dip in customer traffic.
Summer Discount Sale
Summer Cleaning Sale
20% Off Coupon
valid through August
* Please present this flyer
Dry cleaning does not
eliminate sweat stains and smells!
In order to get sweat particles
out of clothes completely,
wet (water) cleaning is best!
Please give our
wet cleaning service a try!
I distribute my flyers by hand to people
who live in the neighborhood.
Personally, I prefer to meet people
at their front door as much as possible
Coming.
Oh! Hello, Kinme-san.
Hello.
so I can hand them a flyer in person.
I'm having a sale right now,
so please take advantage of it.
My!
Thank you for dropping this off.
I'm sure I'll have something for you soon.
Great! Just give me a call.
Oh, Kinme-san! Good afternoon.
Good afternoon.
Oh, right.
I'm holding a sale right now.
Would you like a coupon?
Oh, thank you.
I'll definitely be using you again.
Gift Shop
Atsuei Dried Fish Shop
Good afternoon.
Delivery from Kinme Cleaning.
Oh, welcome back.
I've brought the item
you left with me the other day.
Also this, if you're interested.
My!
Thank you so much!
Oh, it's the big catch banner
she took away to wash.
Now that it's all cleaned up,
why don't we hang it up again?
Yes, I suppose we should.
Well?
Oh my!
It is wonderful!
Thank you so much, dear.
I know how valuable it is to you.
You might be getting another
phone call from Nairo sometime,
but I hope you don't mind.
All right! You can count on Kinme.
It feels nice!
Um...
Huh? Oh! I just needed a way
to get out of the rain!
Hmm?
Oh, sorry. Can I help you?
I haven't visited in a while,
but it sure is a lot fancier than before.
Yes, that's what I hear.
I don't know how the station used to be,
but sometimes I start to wonder.
I've got an old picture.
See? There it is.
We visited once before
when my daughter was still a child.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, I think I remember
something like that.
What a lovely memory.
The festival is only one week away now.
Try to match everyone else's rhythm.
Tam, tam! Tam!
They sure are practicing hard.
Oh.
That reminds me!
When I can hear that sound
coming from around the city,
it really starts to sink in
that it's summertime again.
I wonder how many times
I've climbed up on the roof like this.
I think I came up twice
to watch fireworks.
Otherwise...
Oh, I forgot! I haven't finished
making the poster yet!
Off I go.
Offering
Summer Discount Sale
Everyone with a flyer can receive
You'll also receive
a special extra something
for the season.
Valid Through August
Translation:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michael Arnold
Ashley Barboza
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Riley Dalton
Sriram Gurunathan
On a break
Well, that explains it!
So I wanted to ask, how do you
spend your days off, Kinme-san?
Well, let's see.
I clean the shop, pass out sale flyers,
and make posters and things.
But that's just another workday!
Hmm. You might be right.
Oh, I know! Next time,
you want to try some volleyball?
Huh? Volleyball?
Yeah! I play ladies' volleyball.
I thought you might wanna give it a shot.
I have a feeling
you've got a talent for sports.
I bet you'd catch on quickly.
I wonder, though.
Do you really think I'd be any good?
I'm telling you, you'd be great!
And after volleyball, the members all
go out together to relax at a hot spring!
There's nothing better than
a hot spring after some exercise!
Hot spring? That does sound nice.
Looks like you'd be more interested
in the hot spring part.
But just think about it, okay?
Sure!
Episode 4 A Personal Request from Kinme
Next time is
"A personal request from Kinme."